STEVEN MODIMO

Full Stack Web Developer



- ✓ freelancer.stevenmodimo@gmail.com
- +255746594790
- Arusha, Tanzania
- EstebanPierre
- steven10#6248

I am full stack web developer with experience in building web based online solutions that can impact business and provide help to groups in need all over the world. I like to build stuffs that impact people on various aspects of life.



Skills

Web apps

I can build websites from the user interface to a complete backend system with database intergrations

API Design



d Interests

Reading

Writing

Cooking



Education

Computer Science, **Arusha Technical College** 10/2020 - 06/2022

Online Bootcamp, freecodecamp.org 2019 – 2021



Professional Experience

Lupenet, Backend Developer 2021 - 2021 | Nairobi, Kenya

Habari Node, Full stack engineer 2021 – 2022 | Kampala, Uganda

Tech One, Database Administrator 2022 – present | Nairobi, Kenya

	_		
3	lan	gua	MAC
7	Lali	zua	とヒコ
•		0	o

English	
Swahili	

Certificates

- Backend Developer and API Designer ☑
- Frontend Developement Libraries
- Responsive Web Desing ☑
- Javascript Developer ☑